<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Supratik Das</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Supratik Das</description>
    <generator>Hugo - gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <contact>rick.das08@gmail.com</contact>
    <copyright>© <a href="https://github.com/supra08">Supratik Das</a> 2020</copyright>
    
        <atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 May 2020 05:14:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <author>Supratik Das</author>
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content>&lt;p&gt;Damn, again that awkward and boring about page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Obviously you expect me to greet you as usual, so,&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hello there!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Now you expect me to tell you about myself, which you don’t give a damn about. But out of courtesy that you visited this page, let me continue…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a 3rd year student at Indian Institute of Technology, Roorkee, pursuing my BTech in Electronics and Communication Engineering. I’ve been quite passionate about computers, electronics and in general technology since my childhood days. I really like building ‘things’ and also breaking them apart. I once came across a dusty, downtrodden piece of tutorial on the internet (of course, where else you thought!) and built my first game when I was 13.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The school curriculum introduced me to QBASIC (yeah, that game was in QBASIC), Visual Basic and Java and I taught myself C++, HTML/CSS and JS. In college, I’ve explored quite a few domains of software development, harbouring a keen interest in cloud computing, networking and recently distributed computing. I’ve also been involved in information security as well with a particular interest in web and network security.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s weird that you haven’t complained about the monotonicity yet, so let&amp;rsquo;s continue a bit further. But I will keep it crisp, I promise.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;On campus, I am a part of a group, &lt;a href=&#34;https://sdslabs.co/&#34;&gt;SDSLabs&lt;/a&gt;, whose members are constantly developing awesome softwares and fostering technical activities and innovation on the campus. I am also a part of &lt;a href=&#34;https://infoseciitr.in/&#34;&gt;InfosecIITR&lt;/a&gt;, a group of individuals who participate in CTFs (read cybersecurity competitions) and propagate cybersecurity knowledge in general.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ah so you made it! The one last round and you can leave this page :P&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So apart from software development and websec, the other thing I am really passionate about is music, especially guitars. I like experimenting with them and composing mini riffs and pieces. I am a basketball and snooker fan (and I do play too, at least the latter) and have quite been into room escape puzzles.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Check out my &lt;a href=&#34;/&#34;&gt;blog posts&lt;/a&gt; and my &lt;a href=&#34;/resume.pdf&#34;&gt;resume&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blogs</title>
      <link>/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>Supratik Das</author>
      <guid>/blog/</guid>
      <description></description>
      
      <content></content>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>