<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Supratik Das</title>
    <link>https://supratikdas.com/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Supratik Das</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 04:05:35 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://supratikdas.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>GSOC 2020 Final Assessment - CD Foundation [Screwdriver.cd]</title>
      <link>https://supratikdas.com/blog/gsoc-2020-final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2020 04:05:35 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://supratikdas.com/blog/gsoc-2020-final-report/</guid>
      <description>GSOC 2020 had been a wonderful experience where I got to work on really interesting projects and tasks. Firstly, I would like to thank my mentors, Jithin Emmanuel and Tiffany Kyi for all the technical help, clearing roadblocks and important decision-making throughout the project, both before and during the programme. The same goes to all the PR reviewers from the organization for giving useful insights in the task.
For GSOC, there were two projects to be taken up:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gasper Part 1</title>
      <link>https://supratikdas.com/blog/gasper-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2020 20:34:39 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://supratikdas.com/blog/gasper-part-1/</guid>
      <description>This blog is a cross post from the SDSLabs blog post and is Part 1 of a series. It gives an idea of Gasper’s architecture, technical stack, and capabilities. The subsequent parts cover the detailed discussion of its various components.*
Introduction Providing simplicity without letting go of the necessities in deployments has always been a bottleneck for PaaS providers. Imagine you have a couple of Bare-Metal servers or Virtual Machines at your disposal (collectively called here as nodes) and you wanted to setup an application hosting service, such that the load is evenly distributed among all nodes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>